Guide to the Franklin Bowditch Dexter Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Files on Alumni, Circa 1701-1912; Series I; 9' (22 boxes)
  - Conant, Roger. 1765 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Conant, Shubael. 1732 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    See also: West, Nathaniel, box 18, folder 216.
  - Condit, Charles. 1848 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Cone, Edward. 1851 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Cone, Francis Hiram. 1818 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Cone, Jonathan. 1808
    See: Cone, Edward, box 5, folder 43.
  - Congdon, Albert William. 1879p (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Conner, Lemuel Parker. 1845 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Conner, Samuel Shepard. 1806 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Converse, George Sherman. 1850 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Conwell, Miers Clark. 1852 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Cook, Daniel. 1787 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Cook, Isaac Wayland. 1864l (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Cooke, Daniel. 1780 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Cooke, Daniel. 1787
    See: Cooke, Justus, box 20, folder 239.
  - Cooke, Enos. 1785 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Cooke, James Clarke. 1811 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Cooke, Joseph Platt. 1863 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Cooke, Justus. 1779
  - Cooke, Nathaniel Bowen. 1847m (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Cooke, Oliver Daniel. 1786 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Cooke, Rozelle. 1777
  - Cooke, Samuel. 1705 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Cooley, James. 1814 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Cooley, Timothy Mather. 1792 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Cooper, Jacob. 1852 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Cooper, James Wesley. 1865 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Copland, Alexander. 1814 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Corbyn, Almon David. 1838 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    See also: Walker, Joseph Knox, box 18, folder 211.
  - Cornwall, John Alfred. 1818m (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Cornwell, Francis Edward. 1842 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Cornwell, Wait. 1782 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Cortelyou, Adrian Voorhees. 1863 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Corwin, Joseph A. 1835m (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Cosad, Willis Gaylord. 1888 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Cotes, Christopher. 1829h (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Cothren, Nathaniel. 1850h (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Cothren, William. 1847h (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Cotton, John. 1847 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Councilman, John Thomas. 1839 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Couper, Hamilton. 1849 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Couper, James Hamilton. 1814 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Cowles, Albert Sinclair. 1829 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Cowles, David Smith. 1847h
  - Cowles, Edward Luman. 1872 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Cowles, Edward Sheffield. 1873 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Cowles, Isaac. 1770
    See: Adams, William, box 1, folder 1.
  - Cowles, John Phelps. 1826 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Cowles, Orson. 1828 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Cowles, Samuel Hooker. 1821 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Cowles, Thomas. 1829 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Cox, Adam Tunno. 1821 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Cox, Christopher Christian. 1835 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Crafts, Ebenezer. 1759 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Cragin, Charles Adams. 1873p (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Craig, Simeon Allen. 1847 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Crane, Eliezer. 1826 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Crane, James Burnet. 1838 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Crane, John. 1813
    See: box 20, folder 240.
  - Crane, Matthias. 1747
  - Craw, William Jarvis. 1852 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Creighton, Hamilton. 1852 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Croizer, Robert. 1824 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Crosby, John Player. 1802p (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Crosby, Platt Hiram. 1812 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Crouch, Henry Cooper. 1879 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Crump, John Guy. 1879h (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Crump, William Cleaveland. 1836 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    See also: Richards, Guy, box 15, folder 167.
  - Cuddeback, Thomas. 1847m (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Culber, Moses. 1853h (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Culbertson, William Benton. 1858l (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Cumings, George Washington. 1847 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Cunningham, James. 1875p (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Cunningham, John Moffat. 1876p
  - Currier, John Morrill. 1833 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Curtis, George Edward. 1882 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Curtis, Holbrook. 1807
  - Curtis, Josiah. 1840 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Curtis, William Mark. 1842m (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Curtiss, Erastus. 1821m (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Curtiss, John. 1719 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Curtiss, Sheldon Clark. 1807
  - Cuthbert, James. 1813 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Cutler, James Perrine. 1843 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Cutler, Rufus Putnam. 1839 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Cutler, William Ward. 1831 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Cuyler, Theodore DeWitt. 1882 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Daggett, David. 1782
  - Daggett, Henry. 1771 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Daggett, Leonard Augustus. 1807 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Dana, Daniel. 1782 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Dana, Sylvester. 1826 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Danielson, William. 1811 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Darby, John. 1748 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Darling, David. 1779 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Darling, Noyes. 1801 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Darling, Thomas. 1803 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Darlington, William. 1848h (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Darrach, James. 1827 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Darlington, John. 1806 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Darrow, Amos Smith. 1847 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Dart, Joseph Warren. 1875 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Davenport, Philip Allen. 1837 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Davie, Winston Jones. 1845 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Davies, Thomas. 1758 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Davies, Thomas Frederick. 1813 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    See also: Adams, Ebenezer Banks, box 1, folder 1.
  - Davis, Anthony. 1737 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Davis, David. 1825m (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Davis, George Malin. 1839 non-graduate (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Davis, Henry Gossett. 1839m (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Davis, James. 1815
  - Davis, Samuel Rodney. 1835 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Dawson, Arnoldus Vanderhost. 1837 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Dawson, James Martin. 1884 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Day, Benjamin. 1768
  - Day, Caleb. 1818 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Day, Jeremiah. 1795 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Day, Thomas. 1797 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Dayton, Ralph. 1836 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Dean, Barzillai. 1737 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    See also: Dean, Seth, box 6, folder 50.
  - Dean, James Jarman. 1845 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Dean, Philotus. 1843 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Dean, Richard Crain. 1853h
  - Dean, Seth. 1738 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Deane, St. George. 1809 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - DeForest, George Frederick. 1883 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - DeForest, John Kinne Hyde. 1868 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - DeForest, Othniel. 1847 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Delafield, Edward. 1812 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Deming, Henry Champion. 1836 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Deming, William. 1811 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Denison, Andrew Clark. 1847 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Denison, Charles. 1796 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Denison, Ebenezer. 1827 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Denison, Henry Waldo. 1841 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Denison, Jesse. 1756 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Denniston, John. 1807 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Denniston, William Scott. 1853 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Dering, Nicoll Havens. 1813 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Dershimer, Archibald Alexander. 1878 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Deshon, Francis Bureau. 1820 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Deshon, Giles Henry. 1840 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Devereux, Thomas Pollock. 1813 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Devotion, John. 1786 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Devotion, Samuel Huntington. 1806 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Dewey, Joshua. 1787 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Dewing, Clark. 1874 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - DeWitt, Peter. 1799 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - DeWolf, Allen Monroe. 1827 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - DeWolf, Carlton Melville. 1888p (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - DeWolf, Daniel. 1747 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - DeWolf, Nathan. 1743 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Dexter, Franklin Bowditch. 1861
    See: Woodbridge, William, box 19, folder 230.
  - Dexter, Morton. 1867 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Dexter, Theodore. 1812 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Dibble, Ebenezer. 1734
    See: Clarke, Richard, box 20, folder 239.
  - Dibble, John. 1758
    See: box 20, folder 241.
  - Dickinson, Baxter. 1817 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Dickinson, Edward. 1823m (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Dickinson, John. 1827 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Dickinson, John Dean. 1785 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Dickinson, Jonathan. 1731 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Dickinson, Richard William. 1823 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Dickinson, Rudolphus. 1805 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Dickson, Andrew Flinn. 1845 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Dickson, Charles. 1832 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Dickson, David. 1808h (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Dickson, John. 1814 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    See also: Allen, Edward, box 1, folder 2.
  - Dickson, Samuel Henry. 1814 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Diefendorf, Sanders. 1838 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Diggens, John. 1740 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Dimmick, Alpheus. 1810 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Dimmick, Walter Erskine. 1878 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Dimock, Samuel R. 1847 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Dimon, Theodore. 1835 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Dixon, David Raymond. 1807 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Dixon, Robert. 1829 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Dixon, Simeon Field. 1822 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Dodge, David Stuart. 1826m (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Doggett, Herbert. 1885 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Donaghe, William Rice. 1852 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Donelson, John Samuel. 1854 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Doolittle, Benjamin. 1793 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Doolittle, Jotham Ives. 1795 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Dorsey, Samuel Worthington. 1830 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Douglas, George. 1849 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Douglas, Southerland. 1822
    See: White, Henry, box 21, folder 258.
  - Douglas, William Kirtland. 1851 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Douglass, David Bates. 1813 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Douglass, John Bannab. 1852 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Douw, John De Peyster. 1777 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Dow, Charles Ferdinand. 1853 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Dow, Hendricus. 1784 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Dowe, Joseph Clark. 1846h (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Downing, Eleazar Butler. 1833h
    See: Tyler, Lemuel, box 17, folder 207.
  - Downing, Francis Urquhart. 1872
  - Downing, Lemuel Tyler. 1838 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    See also: Tyler, Lemuel, box 17, folder 207.
  - Downs, Myron. 1830m (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Drake, Carlton Fyler. 1877l
    See: Tuttle, Oswin Hinckley, box 17, folder 207.
  - Drake, Frederick Richard Sewell. 1867 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Draper, Nathaniel. 1745 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Drew, George Washington. 1870 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Driggs, Asa Johnson. 1826m (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Drury, Asa. 1829 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - DuBois, Henry Augustus. 1864h (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - DuBois, Robert Ogden. 1883p (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Dubose, Isaac. 1825 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Dubose, William. 1807 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Dudley, Asahel. 1769 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Duffield, Divie Bethune. 1840 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Duffield, George. 1837 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Duke, Basil. 1845 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Duncan, Alexander. 1825 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Duncan, Lucius Campbell. 1821 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Dunkel, John Lewis. 1836 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Dunkin, Christopher. 1839h (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Dunlap, Ira. 1856 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Dunlap, Thomas. 1812 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Dunning, Benjamin. 1759 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Dunning, William Burr. 1863 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Dunscomb, Josiah William. 1801 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Durand, Alexis Daniel. 1814 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Dutch, Aaron Hardy. 1829 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Dutton, Aaron Rice. 1837 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Dutton, Ebenezer. 1787 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Dutton, Matthew Rice. 1808
  - Dutton, Thomas Rice. 1837 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Dutton, Warren. 1797 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Dutton, Warren B. 1829 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Duvillard, John Antoine. 1854p
  - Dwight, Edwin Welles. 1809 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Dwight, James Henry. 1852 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Dwight, Jonathan. 1768 non-graduate (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Dwight, Josiah. 1794 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Dwight, Louis. 1813 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Dwight, Sereno Edwards. 1803 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Dwight, Timothy. 1744
    See: Tyler, Bennett, box 17, folder 207.
  - Dwight, Timothy. 1769 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Dwight, William White. 1826 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Dyer, Jabez. 1777 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Eames, Theodore. 1809 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Eames, Waldo Chapin. 1881 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Eastman, Ornan. 1841
    See:Woodbridge, William, box 19, folder 230.
  - Easton, Henry Clay. 1876 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Eaton, William Pierce. 1837 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Ebbetts, John Jacob Astor. 1832 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Ebell, Adrian John. 1866p (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Eccles, John Dicks. 1815 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Eddy, Henry. 1832 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Edmiston, Joseph William. 1817 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Edmond, David. 1796 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Edson, Adam. 1775 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Edwards, Daniel. 1720 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Edwards, David Shelton. 1814 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Edwards, Hosea. 1825m (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Edwards, Jonathan. 1720
    See: Smith, William (1719), box 16, folder 188.
  - Edwards, Jonathan. 1769h (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Edwards, Jonathan. 1819
    See: Smith, James Mongin, box 16, folder 186.
  - Edwards, Joseph. 1806 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Edwards, Samuel Henry. 1850 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Edwards, Samuel Lynson. 1812 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Edwards, Tyron Holkar. 1868 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Edwards, Walter. 1820 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Egan, George Clarence. 1879p (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Eggleston, Ambrose. 1813 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Egleston, Melville. 1886h (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Elderkin, Bela. 1767 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Elderkin, John. 1765 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Elderkin, Joshua. 1748 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Eldridge, Charles. 1835h (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Eliot, Jared. 1706 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Elles, Edward. 1843 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Elles, Samuel. 1765 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Elles, William Woodward. 1833 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Elliot, Achilles Henry. 1802 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Elliot, George Augustus. 1813 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Elliot, Harvey, 1805
  - Elliot, John. 1794 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Elliot, William Horace. 1844 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Ellis, Jonathan. 1786 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Ellsworth, Henry Leavitt. 1810 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Ellsworth, Joseph. 1825 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Ellsworth, Stukely. 1847 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Elmer, Daniel. 1713 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Ely, Charles. 1825 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Ely, David. 1769 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    See also: Ely, William Watson, box 7, folder 62.
    See also: Silliman, Gold Selleck (1796), box 16, folder 182.
  - Ely, David. 1800
    See: Ely, William Watson, box 7, folder 62.
  - Ely, Elias Hubbard. 1810 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Ely, Ezra Stiles. 1804 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    See also: Ely, Zebulon, box 7, folder 62.
  - Ely, James. 1831h (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Ely, John. 1786
  - Ely, Jonathan Sturges. 1845 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Ely, Joseph Merrick. 1829 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Ely, Josiah Griffin. 1854m (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Ely, Richard. 1785 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Ely, Simon. 1745 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Ely, Sumner. 1804 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Ely, William. 1787 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Ely, William Watson. 1834m (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Ely, Zebulon. 1779 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Emerson, Alfred. 1834 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Emerson, Joseph. 1830 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Emerson, Rockwell. 1844 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Emigh, Ward. 1845 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Emmons, Julius. 1863 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Engs, George. 1860 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Erving, Joel Fuller. 1842m (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Estes, Daniel Gordon. 1839 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Esty, Isaac. 1821 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Evans, Edward John. 1857 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Evans, Evander Wilhelm. 1851 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Evans, Gurdon. 1850h
    See: box 20, folder 242.
  - Evertson, Nicholas. 1787 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Ewing, Alexander Hamilton. 1869 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Ewing, Martin Baum. 1855 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Fanning, Edmund. 1757 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Fanning, Phineas. 1769 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Farrand, Daniel. 1743 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    See also: Cole, Matthew, box 5, folder 42.
  - Faulkner, Henry Jackson. 1870 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Faulkner, Lester Bradner. 1859 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Faulkner, Samuel Dorr. 1859
    See:box 20, folder 242.
  - Fay, Charles Miles. 1825m (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Fay, Jonathan Prescott. 1827m (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Fearing, Benjamin. 1776 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Fearn, J. Walker Southwayd. 1851 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Felder, John Henry. 1844 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Felder, John Myers. 1804 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Felder, Nathaniel Frederick. 1822 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Fellowes, Richard Simpson. 1832 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Fellows, George Otis. 1886 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Fellows, John. 1783 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Fenn, Benjamin. 1725
  - Fenn, Charles Merwin. 1858 non-graduate (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Fenn, Elisha Rexford. 1815 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Fenn, Horatio Nelson. 1823m (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Fenn, Stephen. 1849 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Ferguson, John Day. 1853l (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Ferry, Lyman Stewart. 1867p (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - FewSmith, Joseph. 1840 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Field, Burr Kellogg. 1877p (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Field, David Dudley. 1802
  - Field, Junius Leavenwoth. 1831m (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Field, Maunsell Bradhurst. 1841 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Field, Seth. 1732
  - Field, Timothy. 1795 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Finch, Sherman. 1828 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    See also:Wright, Charles, box 19, folder 233.
  - Finney, Edgar Augustus. 1860 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Fish, Eliakim. 1760 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Fish, Howland. 1809 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Fisher, George Whitefield. 1859 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Fisher, James Cogswell. 1826 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Fisher, Oscar. 1836 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Fisher, Samuel Ware. 1835 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Fisk, Benjamin. 1747 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Fisk, Robert Farris. 1844 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Fiske, Phineas. 1704 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Fitch, Augustus Benjamin. 1855 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Fitch, Eleazar Thompson. 1810 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Fitch, Ephraim. 1756 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Fitch, George. 1801
  - Fitch, John. 1803
  - Fitch, Lucius Wooster. 1840
  - Fitch, Samuel. 1742 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Flagg, Henry Collins. 1811 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Flagg, Hezekiah. 1800 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Flagg, Levi Wells. 1839
  - Fleming, Peter. 1760 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Fleming, William Bennett. 1825 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Fleming, William Stuart. 1838 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Fletcher, Arthur. 1836 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Fletcher, Samuel Hazzleton. 1824 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Flint, Abel. 1785
  - Foot, Jared. 1820 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Foot, Jared Alfred. 1823 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Foote, Emerson Young. 1879p (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Foote, Henry Hawley. 1850m (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Foote, Horace. 1820 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Foote, John. 1857m (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Foote, William Henry. 1816 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Forbes, Alexander. 1811 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Ford, Seabury. 1825 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Foster, Eleazar. 1802 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Foster, Frank Wade. 1874 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Foster, Lemuel. 1828 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Foster, Stephen Clark. 1840 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Foster, Thomas Edwin. 1840 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Foster, William. 1874 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Fowler, Abraham. 1775 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Fowler, Andrew. 1783 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Fowler, Bancroft. 1796 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Fowler, Daniel Frederick. 1893l (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Fowler, John Douglass. 1813
  - Fowler, John Hart. 1790 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Fowler, Orin. 1815 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Fowler, Stephen. 1779 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Fowler, William. 1860
  - Fox, James Angel. 1816 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Francke, Joaquin John. 1877p (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Franklin, George Mayer. 1858 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Franklin, Sidney Smith. 1826 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Freeland, James. 1875p (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Freeman, George Rudolph. 1885d (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Freeman, Nathaniel. 1805 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - French, Joseph Shelton. 1853 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - French, Lewis. 1821m (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Fries, Henry Chambers. 1882 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Frisbie, Jonathan. 1778 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Frost, Edward. 1820 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Frost, Hezekiah. 1802 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Fuller, Alonzo. 1842m (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Fuller, Asa Witter. 1839m (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Fuller, Caleb. 1758 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Fuller, Daniel. 1721, 1762, 1798 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Fuller, Daniel. 1762 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Fuller, Daniel. 1798 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Fuller, Daniel. 1808
    See: Dunlap, Thomas, box 6, folder 57.
  - Fuller, Israel. 1782 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Fuller, Oliver. 1762 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Fuller, Wilbur Allen. 1875 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Fuller, William. 1825 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Fulton, William Mayo. 1825 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Fyler, John. 1830m (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Gadsden, Christopher Edwards. 1804
    See: Snowden, Charles Blair, box 16, folder 189.
  - Gadsden, Philip. 1820 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Gager, William. 1721 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Gaillard, Richborough. 1844l (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Galatti, Pantoleon G. 1830 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    See also: Galatti, Stephen G., box 8, folder 72.
  - Galatti, Stephen G. 1829 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Gale, Benjamin. 1788 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Gale, LeRoy. 1874p (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Gallaudet, Thomas Hopkins. 1805 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Gallup, James Austin. 1851
  - Gallup, Joseph Henry. 1827 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Gamble, James Matthew. 1867 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Gamble, William. 1871h (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Gardiner, David. 1759 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Gardiner, Hugh Brodie. 1842 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Gardiner, John. 1736 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Gardiner, John Bray. 1840 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    See also: Udall, Richard Athil, box 17, folder 208.
  - Gardiner, John David. 1804 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Gardiner, Samuel L'Hommedieu. 1835 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Gates-Fairbanks, Artemas Wiswall. 1863 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Gay, Fisher. 1759 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Gaylord, Charles Hyde. 1865 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Gaylord, Frederick Arthur. 1886d (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Gaylord, William. 1730 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Geer, Amos. 1757 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Geer, Robert. 1763 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Geis, Silas Wright. 1865l (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Geissenhaimer, Frederick William. 1846l (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - George, William Cornelius. 1762h (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Gere, Edward. 1818 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Gere, William. 1827 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Gibbs, Henry W. 1808 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Gibson, William Miller. 1808 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Gilbert, Edwin Randolph. 1829 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Gilbert, Ezekiel. 1778 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Gilbert, George Alfred. 1822m (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Gilbert, Gershom Clarke Hyde. 1841 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Gilbert, Joseph Morgan. 1818 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Gilbert, Matthew James. 1829 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Gilbert, Theodore. 1825m (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Giles, William. 1763 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Gill, Robert T. 1842 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Gillespie, James Metcalf. 1853 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Gillett, Ezra Hall. 1841 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Gillett, Moses. 1804 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Gilmore, James. 1834 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Glisan, Clarence. 1887 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Glover, Abiel Booth. 1816 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Glynn, James. 1844h (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Gobrecht, Charles Joseph. 1846 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Goddard, Calvin Luther. 1845 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Goddard, Charles. 1826 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Goddard, Charles Backus. 1814 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Goddard, George Calvin. 1820 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Goddard, Levi Hart. 1828 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Goff, Joseph Wadsworth. 1873
    See: Wickham, William, box 18, folder 221.
  - Gold, Hezekiah. 1751 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    See also: Ufford, Hezekiah Gold, box 17, folder 208.
  - Gold, Thomas. 1778 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Gold, Thomas Ruggles. 1786 (Box 8, Folder 76)